Come on, this is unbelievable!
This is stupid!
What has this happened to me?
I think I've got to kill someone.
Well, this is awful.
Apparently there's another
veil centered underneath here.
And this one also traps
non-sorcerous inside.
Excuse me, pardon me. Coming through.
Hmm.
I think I have a good
idea what they're after.
I'll play along.
They're making Gojo do
this all by himself?
I understand the logic, but there has to
be something we can do to help him out.
Be his backup or something, huh?
Yeah, and they agree with you.
That's why we're heading to Shibuya now.
Oh, okay, then give it back!
give it back!
I
Can't believe they're actually
forcing my sister to be his backup?
That's Satoru Gojo thinks he's
some kind of big shot or something.
He is a big shot So you shouldn't just treat
him like he's an ordinary guy You know,
you're not like any ordinary
woman yourself, big sister.
Ah, oui oui.
You are truly adorable,
and that's why I love you.
Here you go, saying
stuff you don't believe.
Because you don't really love your
family members, isn't that right?
You just love that I'm helping
you out with your work right now.
You really do get me.
That's the part of you I
love the best. Oh, boy.
Can we just get back to work?
Hello, Mei Mei here.
Oh?
Itadori, we have a change in plans. Huh?
Another veil like the one over Shibuya
was lowered over Meiji Shrine Station.
We're heading to that one instead.
We're running there, so try to keep up.
You bet!
I see that you're all fully prepared.
You really came!
You won't have any excuses left!
When you lose this time?
And have you given any thought?
To the first excuse you'll use?
When you get beaten by the three of us!
You are my special.
You
are
my special. You
my special.
Now I'm no, Show Show, to do my show!
Oh, go then, set go on the middle!
I won't show you like my rhyme!
Mother laughing את yeah!
You know what it's wrong!
I love you, Baby!
Who can't find more?
What can I do
to my heart?
Here are some seize.
I will blow you!
Don't let you dance.
Don't up your hands.
It should make you die?
You're laveable.
I may go so much!
You are my special.
I am sick Oh no no no, so it's you?
I am in my life.
It should make you cry!
You're laveable.
There's a veil to keep
ordinary people trapped inside,
covering the entire
underground subway station.
And within that veil,
there's another veil
centered around the platform,
on level B5 that prevents
sorcerers from entering.
We believe the cursed spirit
or cursed user who lowered
these veils is located
somewhere between these two.
Between them?
Not on the platform
they're centered around?
Yes, that is correct.
Every time they go outside the
Veil, they're taking on a risk.
It's the only way for them to keep
their barrier fully strengthened.
Two of our assistant supervisors
have already been taken out.
In addition, between these barriers...
I shouldn't say.
It's still just a guess, and
we really can't be certain yet.
That's fine, say it anyway.
It might be helpful.
They are transfigured humans.
Between the barriers.
What are you two doing?
We have to hurry!
Shh.
Can't you see that my sister is
currently sharing the crow's perception?
It's a process that takes
concentration, so be quiet.
It's all right.
I don't mind if you talk.
She says it's fine.
Hey, sis!
Why do you always contradict me?
Hmm.
I've got the gist of it.
Itadori, which would you prefer?
killing lots of weak,
transfigured humans, or exercising
one powerful, cursed spirit.
Knowing you, it's probably the latter.
Here's the map.
It shows the underground station.
The transfigured humans are milling around
and attacking normal
people here on level B4.
The majority of the normal people are
probably at the train platform on level B5.
Probably?
All the crows that I use are
imbued with cursed energy,
so they couldn't enter level B5.
I'm guessing they're forcing
normal people to flee to level B5,
thus serving them up.
Also, my crows got hunted down
here, between levels B1 and B2.
This is likely where the cursed spirit or
cursed user who lowered
the veil is hiding.
Maybe they're planning to hunt down
any humans that come back up to B4.
Maybe it has to do with
the Vale's conditions.
It's not clear to me yet.
Why choose this positioning,
and why isolate Level B5?
He's here, though, right?
He's standing down below us.
It's that curse.
Maybe.
My crows all got killed before they could
confirm if the curse
they saw was Patchface.
However, the presence of transfigured
humans would suggest that it's likely.
I'm not so sure about
dividing up our forces,
but if we keep wasting time, all the
common people on B4 will be wiped out.
The two of us will take
Exit 7 directly to B4.
We'll rescue the civilians
still on that level.
If it gets too dangerous, you
head down there as well, okay?
Though, if I can be greedy,
I hope that by the time we reunite with
each other, the veil will be lifted,
the civilians will be freed?
And we'll finally figure out exactly
what our opponents on level B5 are after.
Don't worry about me, Mei Mei.
I won't lose anymore.
I promise.
Well?
You gonna stop staring while I eat?
Oh, wait.
You're one of those...
Jujutsu...
Jojo Genie.
No, that's not it.
Jujutsu Sorcerer, right?
Jujutsu Sorcerer.
Am I right?
Yeah, I'm right.
I'm pretty clever.
I know the Patchface's cursed
spirit is around here somewhere.
Where is he?
Patchface?
I don't recall the name.
he's the one with
stitches all over his face
don't insult me i know
that much don't forget
i'm clever mahito is
below he told me to stay
here and make sure that i protect the veil
mahito huh i think jiupei called him that
too whatever its name
doesn't matter right now
barriers are pretty complicated
aren't they there are plenty
of people who are strong but
still can't do them although
i'm both strong and capable
this thing is responsible for
the veil both of them doesn't
seem likely mahito sorcery
is very bad very very bad he
did say that he was here to
make sure he protects the veil
which makes that object very
suspicious i'll smash it for
starters did you know a human's
mahito transfigures lose
their flavor quicker than gum
I can tell the difference so easily!
It's because I'm so clever!
I'm tired of hearing
how clever this guy is.
All you curses need to stop
underestimating humans.
I get it you're not clever are you?
Let me ask you something: you
don't know what curse I am! Do you?
Well? Do you?
I didn't think so.
The not so clever ones in this
world are always the first to die.
Huh?
You're a grasshopper curse.
This guy is clever!
Locust Plague A large-scale
disaster arising from an
outbreak of locusts The locusts will
consume not just crops, but paper,
clothes, buildings, anything and
everything made from plant fibers.
A locust is required to eat its own weight
in food every day in order to grow bigger.
So a locust swarm weighing
one ton must consume the
equivalent of 2,500 people's
worth of food each day.
The abnormal sounds of chewing fill the
air around the swarm all day and night.
And once the swarm has passed,
it leaves behind a wasteland covered in
the black fluid secreted by the locusts,
creating a site that is far from tranquil.
Mankind has long feared,
hated, and cursed such demonic pests
throughout the course of recorded history.
What an incredible jaw
and jumping ability.
The fact that it can understand speech
means it's decently powerful too.
Let's go.
All you do is run away from me.
Do you want to fight or don't you?
He probably doesn't have any
tricks he's not showing me.
I don't know yet.
Well, are you clever?
Or are you not clever?
Because you know what?
I'm clever.
I don't think you are.
Clever people don't go around
calling themselves clever.
Why wouldn't they?
Time to go fist to fist, you with
your two arms, this is my war!
My arms, my jaw, and my eyes!
They're all superior to
those of human beings!
So why is this happening?
Why am I the only one getting hit?
Even with that I'm still the more clever
one Locusts lay their eggs underground
To facilitate this they're capable
of extending their abdomens
The tips of which are hard to
nearly three times their normal life
The more clever one wins!
He did have a trick.
But more importantly...
Look at this.
You've eaten people.
You're prepared for
what that means, right?
There was a gap in their strength
that no trick could overcome.
Mei Mei?
Yes.
The veil is lifted.
Let's wait for Itadori,
and then descend to B5.
Kogai was exorcised, I guess.
That means a skilled sorcerer is here.
What a shame.
I wanted to fight them too.
But that's not going to happen now.
Got a job to do.
you!
Just accept it with grace!
Thanks!
I'm so honored!
Guess we're too late.
Hey, you!
Sitting down over there!
Are you okay?
Where are the others?
You don't need to do all this.
I'm not running away.
I mean, if I tried running away,
I'm guessing You guys would
kill every human in here, right?
Well, what are those two
talking about down there?
Don't you mean four?
Would we kill them then?
If you run away.
Do you understand what
will happen when Satoru
Gojo is able to utilize
his power to the fullest?
Quit with the build-up and just say it.
Well, you see...
It gets interesting when he's alone.
The correct answer is...
Whether you run or not!
Get back, folks, or you'll die.
Ah,
so they sealed the exit off
earlier to create a blind spot so
I wouldn't know if there were
people on the other side or not.
Any Jujutsu Sorcerer with him is
basically just a hindrance to his actions.
So we'll go one step lower and completely
surround him with non-sorcerers instead.
Blood manipulation.
Slicing exorcism.
The minimum output of his curse technique
reversal is double that
of his amplification.
It'll be nearly impossible for him to use
it without catching
non-sorcerers in it too.
He probably won't be able to charge his
blue up to an effective output either.
It should prove difficult for him to use
blue for high-speed movement as well.
It would make him a dump truck as
far as non-sorcerers are concerned.
Get hit, and it's instant death.
So in that situation, Satoru Gojo will
have to focus his energy on defense.
Domain amplification!
That makes sense for you guys.
I suppose you would think of that
after allying with Curse users.
Domain amplification.
It's the same principle as the
new Shadow School Simple Domain.
They envelop themselves
with the domain. Well,
that reduces its guaranteed hit effect and
ensures they neutralize
any technique used.
If they pulled it off right, it
would allow their attacks to hit me.
What do we do about his
domain, Infinite Void?
The only ones unaffected by Infinite
Void are Satoru Gojo himself,
along with anyone he touches.
Even then,
if he does have the skill
to selectively trap each of
you inside one of his powerful
infinite void domains,
a great number of non-sorcerers
would get crushed to
death in the space left between
his domain and the Veil.
I would give it a 99 % chance he
won't use his domain against you.
But that means you mustn't
use your domains either.
If you draw a large mass of
non-sorcerers into your domain,
he'll be forced to give up on
them, and then he'll use his too.
and you already know that
you can't win a tug-of-war of
domains with him at any rate
you just need to get satoru gojo
to focus focus on defeating
cursed spirits and rescuing non
-sorcerers are
you okay come
on now try to keep it together
I don't think you're hurt
Come on, take my hand
I thought that we agreed
you wouldn't run away
Should I keep killing to
make you understand me?
Man, honestly, I'm actually
shocked Oh, really?
Here come the excuses
Not at all, Blood
I'm saying I'm actually
shocked you would ever
have thought you could beat
me with this loser shit.
I want you to hold out for
at least 20 minutes or so.
After that, it's my turn.
That's when I'll unleash
the prison realm on him.
Thank you.
I have to choose the right world.
It's easy to choose.
I'm going to make a good place.
If you don't have anything,
I'll believe
in
yourself.
So, keep it on the key to the pain.
The world is still there.
Just be by yourself.
I'm living more than once.
It's the Yamanote Lion Game, and
the topic is Gojo's Good Qualities!
Yay!
Strong! Strong.
Only strong!
Next time, Shibuya Incident, gate open.
And so rich.
Aw, you're such a jokester!
I mean, she ain't lying.